PROFILE

With my knowledge, skills, and ability to deliver the best to the company, with the expertise of experience in this new era of dimensions and the changing market needs, trends, and demands of the customers. I will bring out the best for this company in this In-block transaction period.

CONTACT

PHONE: 9104933397

EMAIL:

gauravlanghnojia@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Music Cricket Writing Chess

Reading Movies

Leadership

SKILLS

Cross-Functional Negotiation 0 & M Networking CRM Meta Analytics Google Analytics MS Office Sales and Marketing Digital Marketing SEO (On Page/ Off Page) Social Media Marketing Transcription Backlinking AdSense AdWords (Google Ads) Affiliate Marketing WordPress

LINKS

LinkedIn Profile

www.linkedin.com/comm/mynetwork/discove ry-see-

all?usecase=PEOPLE_FOLLOWS&followMembe r=gaurav-l-50583a203

Articles:

https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/what-cashflow-statement-comprehensive-guide-indiangaurav-langhnojia-mmozf/

https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/research-2047-vision-where-india-before-headedfuture-langhnojia-drjuc/

Gaurav Langhnojia Content Writing | Digital Marketing | SEO | Backlinks |

EDUCATION

SSC Board [Gujarat Board]

2002 - 2003

HSC Board [Gujarat Board]

2004 - 2005

Bachler's of Commerce [Gujarat University]

2005 - 2008

Diploma in Management

ICFAI Distance Learning Program

Diploma in International Marketing

AMA Association

Digital Marketing Course

I flame Institute.

Google Certified Courses

Work Experience:

Freelance under GAURAM & Co. (June 2018 to till Date) Fusion Factor:

I did a contractual agreement with Fusion Factor, it's a network company where I was looking into Social Media Marketing, weekly Analysis Blog, and its updates on Websites

DrXperts.com:

In this Assignment, I have written 96 1000 to 1200-word articles and uploaded them on the company website.

J Global Solutions:

I have designed an SEO Content Website for an Export company that deals in Indian vegetables and Cereals. However, in 2020, due to the pandemic company was closed, and the website was also closed. I do have Content with me as a work proof.

I have also provided services do to Gusworks, Egyan Hub, DuFlex info and many more

Job Details Health care Industries (Field Work) May 2008 to June 2021:

I have started my career with Cipla Ltd. As a baseline manager, I have ended up with a Business Manager throughout the Journey. During my tenure, I have gained Experience of the Expansion and Retention of my business. Also got rich experience in developing and training the team. With that, I have also organized as well as attended many Seminars (CME/ All India doctors meet). As a Social responsibility, I have also been exposed to organizing camps and clinics for poor patients and providing them with medicine at very minimal rates. These are some of the major companies I have worked with in my 15+ years of Tenure.

Mani Medical India, Axa Parenterals Ltd., Ascensia Diabetes Care, Boehringer Ingelheim, Cipla Ltd.